{
    "question": "Teacher : may i have your attentio,please? students:\u200b",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>Yes,Of course</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>Thanks</p><p>Semoga membantu</p>",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "what-does-the-song-talk-about-756",
            "question": "What does the song talk about\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>which song? lagu yang mana? kamu ga nambahin lagu apa apa</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>artinya:apa yang dibicarakan lagu itu</p><p>nahh jawabannya gak tau harusnya tambahin foto</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "teacher-how-are-you-studentthank-you-828",
            "question": "Teacher :how are you?\r\n Student:.....,thank you",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>i&#039;m fine</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>alternatif lain:</p><p>I am doing fine</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p>I am good, thank you</p><p></p><p>But the answer is depending on how your feeling. If you feel bad than say you aren&#039;t feel good but if you are good then say it that you are feeling good</p><p></p><p>Simple by hucas</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "for-questions-number-18-to-20-complete-the-following-text-with-t-266",
            "question": "For questions number 18 to 20, Complete the following text with the suitable words.    Mr.Komar is an English teacher. He speak English fluently.\r\nHis wife, Mrs. Nani is a(18)......She helps sick people.\r\nShe doesn't speak English. Mr.Komar has two children.\r\nThey study English not only at school but also at home.\r\nThey are(19).....students. Their father teaches them every night,\r\nSo they can speak English (20) ......He is very proud of them.\r\n18. a. teacher\r\nb. janitor\r\nc. doctor\r\nd. chef\r\n19. a. lazy\r\nb. proud\r\nc. stupid\r\nd. diligent\r\n20. a. fluently\r\nb. silently\r\nC. slowly\r\nd. badly\r\nThis text is for questions number 21 to 23.\r\nMy favorite animal is rabbit. Rabit has two longears.\r\nIts eyes are big and black, but when it is dark its eyes are red.\r\nIt has two long teeth Its nose is small and soft pink.\r\nIts tail is soft,round and small like a cotton ball. Its legs are small,\r\nIt doesn't walk, it jumps It is vegetarian and its favorite food is carrct.\r\nRabbits are very cute.\r\n21. How many ears does the rabbit have?\r\na. two ears\r\nc. three ears\r\nb. four ears\r\nd. five ears\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p>18. <strong>C</strong><strong>.</strong><strong> </strong><strong>D</strong><strong>o</strong><strong>c</strong><strong>t</strong><strong>o</strong><strong>r</strong></p><p></p><p><strong>P</strong><strong>e</strong><strong>n</strong><strong>j</strong><strong>e</strong><strong>l</strong><strong>a</strong><strong>s</strong><strong>a</strong><strong>n</strong><strong> </strong><strong>:</strong></p><p>Teks diatas menjelaskan pekerjaan Mrs. Nani yang membantu orang sakit. Jadi, jawabannya adalah <strong>(</strong><strong>C</strong><strong>.</strong><strong>)</strong></p><p></p><p>19. <strong>D</strong><strong>.</strong><strong> </strong><strong>D</strong><strong>i</strong><strong>l</strong><strong>i</strong><strong>g</strong><strong>e</strong><strong>n</strong><strong>t</strong></p><p></p><p><strong>P</strong><strong>e</strong><strong>n</strong><strong>j</strong><strong>e</strong><strong>l</strong><strong>a</strong><strong>s</strong><strong>a</strong><strong>n</strong><strong> </strong><strong>:</strong></p><p>Teks diatas mengatakan mereka selalu belajar Bahasa Inggris setiap malam dan mereka sangat rajin, Jadi jawabannya adalah <strong>(</strong><strong>D</strong><strong>.</strong><strong>)</strong></p><p></p><p>20. <strong>A</strong><strong>.</strong><strong> </strong><strong>F</strong><strong>l</strong><strong>u</strong><strong>e</strong><strong>n</strong><strong>t</strong><strong>l</strong><strong>y</strong></p><p></p><p><strong>P</strong><strong>e</strong><strong>n</strong><strong>j</strong><strong>e</strong><strong>l</strong><strong>a</strong><strong>s</strong><strong>a</strong><strong>n</strong><strong> </strong><strong>:</strong></p><p>Teks diatas mengatakan bahwa Mr. Komar sangat bangga dengan anak-anak nya karena bisa berbahasa Inggris dengan lancar. Jadi jawabannya adalah <strong>(</strong><strong>A</strong><strong>.</strong><strong>)</strong></p><p></p><p>21. How many ears does the rabbit have?</p><p>    : <strong>A</strong><strong>.</strong><strong> </strong><strong>T</strong><strong>w</strong><strong>o</strong><strong> </strong><strong>e</strong><strong>a</strong><strong>r</strong><strong>s</strong></p><p></p><p><strong>P</strong><strong>e</strong><strong>n</strong><strong>j</strong><strong>e</strong><strong>l</strong><strong>a</strong><strong>s</strong><strong>a</strong><strong>n</strong><strong> </strong><strong>:</strong></p><p>Berdasarkan teks diatas, kelinci adalah binatang favorit sang penulis dan kelinci itu mempunyai 2 telinga. Jadi jawabannya adalah <strong>(</strong><strong>A</strong><strong>.</strong><strong>)</strong></p><p></p><p>Maaf kalau ada yang salah dalam penyampaian kata\u00b2nya, apabila ada yang salah dalam jawabannya bisa dikoreksi yaa, semoga membantu ! &lt;3</p><p></p><p>\u2014Miranthi P.</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "write-two-sentences-expressing-what-is-happening-around-you-a-b-378",
            "question": "Write two sentences expressing what is happening around you\r\nA.\r\nB.\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>A. many weddings</p><p>B. always stuck</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "peter-is-the-youngest-in-our-family-he-is-fourteen-years-old-and-662",
            "question": "Peter is the youngest in our family. He is fourteen years old and four years younger than me. He has long, straight hair, bright eyes and a friendly smile. Sometimes he is rather naughty at home, but he usually does what he is asked to do.    Peter is interested in sports very much, and at school, he plays football and tennis. He is the best badminton player in our family.\r\n3. Which of the following statement is not true about Peter\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>gue player old apa gak senang</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "jakarta-isthan-sidoarjo-179",
            "question": "Jakarta is....than sidoarjo",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>big</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>artinya lebih besar</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "besi-tanah-udara-merupakan-contoh-962",
            "question": "Besi tanah udara merupakan contoh\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>benda yang dapat di perbarui</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>maaf jika salah:)</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "10-which-statement-is-not-true-based-in-on-the-text-a-dina-got-777",
            "question": "10. Which statement is NOT TRUE    based in on the text?\r\na. Dina got up very late\r\nb. Dina did not even have breakfast\r\nc. Dina is as old as her sister\r\nd. Dina took very quick bath\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>A. Dina got very late</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>SORRY BANGET KALAU SALAH</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "soal-choose-the-correct-answer-by-crossing-abc-ord-ana-edi-the-849",
            "question": "SOAL    Choose the correct answer by crossing a,b,c ord!\r\nAna\r\nEdi\r\nThe following conversation is used to answer questions number 1-5\r\n: This park is shadyand the flowers are colorful.I (1).....this park\r\n: I do,too. This is a (2).....park\r\nMono : Look!There are butterflies.\r\n: They are(3) ....\r\n: There are garbage cans too. We can keep this park(4) ..\r\n: I like studying here. The weather is nice. The park is beautiful.\r\nAnd it's a (5).....\r\nPutri\r\nAdi\r\nEni\r\n1. a. want to go\r\nb. hate\r\nc. like\r\nd. feel\r\n2. a. ugly\r\nb. dirty\r\nc. city\r\nd. wonderful\r\n3. a. flyng\r\nb. boring\r\nc. pretty\r\nd. dirty\r\n4. a. dirty\r\nb. clean\r\nc. ugly\r\nd. wonderful\r\n5. a. terrible\r\nb. horrible\r\nc. beautiful\r\nd. pret\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>1. c. like</p><p>2. d. beautiful</p><p>3. c. pretty</p><p>4. b. clean</p><p>5. d. pretty</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "how-did-you-say-to-compare-animal-433",
            "question": "How did you say to compare animal",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>Bagaimana Anda mengatakan untuk membandingkan hewan</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>tuh artinya</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>adalah hai</p><p> kamu namanya siapa</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}